nonkers.com 2016-05-30

# Privacy Policy – Latest Hollywood Gossip, US Celebrity Gossip, Celebrity News | Gossip Tracker

This policy covers how GossipTracker.com (“GossipTracker.com”) treats information which personally identifies you (personal information) that GossipTracker.com collects and receives. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. Once you provide GossipTracker.com with personal information, you are not anonymous to us.

There are several links from the GossipTracker.com site to third party information and service providers who may collect personal information from you in order to provide you with information or services. GossipTracker.com has no control over the privacy policy of any third party company, so please examine their privacy policy prior to submitting any personal information. This privacy policy only applies to the GossipTracker.com web site.

Information Collection and Use

General:

When you read stories at GossipTracker.com, GossipTracker.com does not collect any personal information from you.

GossipTracker.com collects personal information when you submit feedback or enter a contest. We may also receive personal information from you, for example when you: respond to an email requesting feedback.

When you visit GossipTracker.com pages, we may collect certain information about your visit from your browser, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet, the date and time you access the GossipTracker.com site, the pages that you access while at the GossipTracker.com site and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to the GossipTracker.com site. GossipTracker.com aggregates non-specific visitor information for statistical purposes, such as which stories are most popular, and which stories are read more frequently.

This information is used to help improve the GossipTracker.com site, analyze trends, and administer the site.

GossipTracker.com uses your personal information for the following general purposes: to determine a winner to contests, to respond to your feedback and to alert you of winners to a contest you’ve entered. In addition, we use your information to send out our weekly newsletter.

GossipTracker.com uses aggregate and non-personal information to conduct research and to provide reports for GossipTracker.com business partners and customers.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

GossipTracker.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

You elect to receive information from contest sponsors by checking the “opt in” box for that contest. GossipTracker.com will share your personal information only as you have elected.

Advertisements served by third party Internet advertising technology companies, appear on pages throughout the GossipTracker.com site. Some advertisements may request personal information directly from you or take you to web sites that may request your personal information.  
GossipTracker.com has no control over its advertisers’ privacy policies, so please examine the privacy policy of any company  
advertising on the GossipTracker.com site prior to submitting any personal information. In addition, some ad-serving companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and may use information about your visits to the GossipTracker.com site and other web sites  
in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Please be aware that when you provide personal information to GossipTracker.com and authorize GossipTracker.com to share the information with a third party, your personal information becomes the property of GossipTracker.com and/or the third party. GossipTracker.com and/or the third party may use your personal information to process your request and provide valuable services. GossipTracker.com will only share your personal information with third parties under a confidentiality agreement or similar arrangement that restricts the third party from sharing your personal information with others.

If you do not want your information to be used for marketing by or a third party, do not “opt in” or agree to such use when you provide your personal information through the GossipTracker.com site. If you do not want your non-specific information used for marketing please do not submit your information through our contests.

Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

Cookies

GossipTracker.com lets other companies, including business partners and companies that show advertisements on some of our pages, set and  
access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies.

Advertisers or other companies may have access to GossipTracker.com’s cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline these cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other web sites you visit.

Protection of Minor’s Personal Information

GossipTracker.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

GossipTracker.com may occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy policy. If we make such changes to this privacy policy, we will place a prominent notice at the top of the privacy policy and you will also see the word “Updated” next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of the GossipTracker.com site. We encourage you to  
periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your  
continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any up-dates.

Social Media:

Our Websites contain several links to or integrations with other websites, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Disqus, Tumblr, etc., whose information practices may be different from ours.

GossipTracker.com, its officers, directors, partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, agents, representatives, vendors or suppliers are responsible for the content, privacy policies, products, services, reliability, viewpoint or accuracy of information on any such websites. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our Websites or integrations with other websites have separate privacy policies.

We have no responsibility or liability for the policies implemented by third parties on their websites. You should contact those third parties directly to ask questions about their privacy policies.

If you enter or choose to leave our sites and go to outside websites, your visits and actions on those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  
We do not control and are not responsible for the collection of personal information by third party websites, including websites owned or controlled by our preferred financial partners, advertisers, vendors and/or websites not controlled or authorized by GossipTracker.com. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our Websites or integrations with other websites have separate privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the policies implemented by third parties on their websites. You should contact those third parties directly to ask questions about their privacy policies.

If you enter or choose to leave our Websites via links to other non-GossipTracker.com websites, your visits and actions on those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please contact us.
